dailyindia.com 2017-02-09

# DailyIndia.com Privacy Policy

DailyIndia.com (the "Site") believes in protecting your personally identifiable information, while also offering you a high quality experience with this Site. 

**Information Sharing**

We do not rent, sell, or share your personal information with any third party. We may bring you selected offers from third parties, but all such offers shall be transmitted from the Site, and the third party shall not have access to your personal information. 

**Cookies  
**

We may set cookies on your computers. Cookies are small computer files set on your computer that can store, and sometimes track, information about you. You can, of course, disable cookies on your browser, but you may be required to re-enter information onto the Site. The Site set cookies do not contain personally identifiable information. 

**Advertisements**

In order to continue to bring you the site for free we place advertising on our web pages. Some of these advertisements, if clicked upon, may contain cookies, collect information, such as your IP address and domain type. You should consult the privacy policies of any advertisers with respect to their information gathering practices.

We partner with ValueClick to serve ads and/or collect certain information when you visit our website. ValueClick may use cookies or web beacons to collect non-personally identifiable information during your visit to this website in order to help show advertisements on other websites likely to be more interesting to you. To learn more about this “behavioral advertising” practice or to opt-out of this use of your anonymous information, you can visit http://valueclickmedia.com/member_privacy.shtml

**Links**  
This Site cotains third party content or services from other websites and may be available to you from a link provided by the Site. Any links or other websites not affiliated with the Site are not subject to this privacy policy.  You should review the terms of use in the privacy policy at any third party's website to determine how that site protects your privacy.  This Site is in no way whatsoever responsible for the content of third party websites or actions of any third parties.

**Updating**  
We reserve the right to update this policy at any time.
